ظآزLove crosses every cycle
of life and deathظآز
ظآزSo let me fall with youظآز
ظآزAll the noise of the mortal worldظآز
ظآزIs nothing compared to her eyesظآز
ظآزWhoever said love itself is sinظآز
ظآزWhen a heartbeat turns into
wind and moonlightظآز
ظآزPainting a banquet
of endless spring bloomsظآز
ظآزHow beautifulظآز
=Blooms for Her=
=Episode 2=
If you like it this way
so be it.
Interesting.
Every time you complete a mission
you will receive a reward.
In six months
you'll get rid of the Lockjaw Drop.
Understood.
(My mother was a princess of Xichu.)
(Ten years ago,)
(she died in a palace fire.)
(Your face is exactly like hers.)
(In the Palace)
(It takes three days to temper jade.)
(Let me see how much trouble)
(this face of yours
can stir in the palace.)
(She... she has no feet.)
(She's floating!)
(Consort Chu!)
(Consort Chu,
who died in a fire, has returned!)
Mother
what expression
do you think they'll have
when they see you again?
From today on
your name is Mei Lin.
And you're the princess of Xichu.
I understand.
I need you to get close to
Prince Xuanlie
at the Drilling Ground tomorrow.
Infiltrate his side
and be my inside source.
(Murong Xuanlie, The Eldest Prince)
(He's ruthless and cruel.)
(Crippled me and cost me the battle.)
(No matter what he does,)
(do not act on your own.)
(Wait for my signal.)
(Of course.)
Hurry, keep up.
Father.
Kneel.
I won a great victory this time
and brought back many Xichu remnants.
Why not let them fight like beasts
(Murong Che, Emperor of Daliang)
to entertain you?
(Pei Du, The Emperor's Confidant)
How come killing a few bound men
awaiting death shows Daliang's might?
Your way of awing the world,
Your Highness,
is truly eye-opening.
(The imperial elite see us
as mere ants,)
(crushing us.)
(But I will carve out
my own path to survive!)
Mr. Pei, you're a civil official.
You don't get it.
Training without bloodshed
isn't training at all.
Xuanlie.
What?
Jinghe, you can't even stand
the blood of Xichu remnants?
Do you still miss your motherland?
Watch your words, Xuanlie.
If that's the case
then prove to Father.
Show him your loyalty to Daliang.
Kill them.
(Clever trap.)
(If Murong Jinghe kills us,)
(the world will call him cruel.)
(If he doesn't,)
(they'll doubt his loyalty to Daliang.)
(He's still useful to me.)
(He must not fall from power again.)
Kill me instead.
I'm Mei Lin, princess of Xichu.
I beg Your Majesty for mercy.
Take my life, and spare these people.
Bring her forward.
Move!
They're alike.
(Consort Li)
They really are.
(Yiyi!)
(Yiyi,)
(have you come back?)
But she's not truly her.
Then let it be as you wish.
Your life for these slaves' lives.
(For revenge,)
(anyone can become my blade,)
(even myself.)
As a princess, I
was sustained by my people.
Giving my own life
to save the commoners
is worth it.
ظآزMoonlight spills like quiet tidesظآز
ظآزA celestial bird
brushes the mountain's edgeظآز
ظآزWings of light drift through the airظآز
ظآزLike blossoms that refuse to fadeظآز
ظآزIt asks no right or wrongظآز
ظآزNor fears the turning of fateظآز
ظآزA trace of spring on the windظآز
ظآزA whisper of a broken heartظآز
ظآزA farewell song unfoldsظآز
ظآزCarrying every sorrow within itظآز
ظآزKarma weaves its endless threadظآز
ظآزAnd I would follow you
without turning backظآز
ظآزLife and death become
nothing sharp or finalظآز
ظآزLove and hate are carried away
on the breezeظآز
ظآزBefore freedom is ever reachedظآز
ظآزOne must first dissolve into tearsظآز
ظآزLove crosses every cycle
of life and deathظآز
ظآزSo let me fall with youظآز
ظآزAll the noise of the mortal worldظآز
ظآزIs nothing compared to her eyesظآز
ظآزWhoever said love itself is sinظآز
ظآزWhen a heartbeat turns into
wind and moonlightظآز
ظآزPainting a banquet
of endless spring bloomsظآز
ظآزHow beautifulظآز
ظآزTwo hearts leaning into one anotherظآز
ظآزPerfectly, impossibly rightظآز